Guide to the Office of Administration and Facilities, Eileen Buckley 1959-1995 (Bulk 1964-1989) RG 8.0 RG 8.0
New York University Archives
- Series I: General Files
  - Heights: Technology 2 - Financing, undated (Box 23, Folder 23)
  - Heights: Technology 2 - Financing, undated (Box 23, Folder 24)
  - Heights: Technology 2 - Landscaping, undated (Box 23, Folder 25)
  - Heights: Technology 2 - Miscellaneous, undated (Box 23, Folder 26)
  - Heights: Techonolgy 2 - Weather Bureau Lease, undated (Box 23, Folder 27)
  - Heights: Tennis Court Proposal, undated (Box 23, Folder 28)
  - Heights: Trustees, undated (Box 23, Folder 29)
  - Heights: Unions, undated (Box 23, Folder 30)
  - Heights: University Heights Council, undated (Box 23, Folder 31)
  - Hellenic Heritage, undated (Box 24, Folder 1)
    barcode: 3 1142 04058451 1
  - Hellenic Heritage, undated (Box 24, Folder 2)
  - Hellenic Heritage Correspondence, undated (Box 24, Folder 3)
  - Hendin, Josephine, undated (Box 24, Folder 4)
  - Henry James Sculpture, undated (Box 24, Folder 5)
  - Henry James Sesquicentennial, undated (Box 24, Folder 6)
  - Henry James Sesquicentennial, undated (Box 24, Folder 7)
  - Hertzberg, Arthur, undated (Box 24, Folder 8)
  - Heyman, George, undated (Box 24, Folder 9)
  - HHS Planning Commission, undated (Box 24, Folder 10)
  - High School Outreach, undated (Box 24, Folder 11)
  - Higher Education Opportunities, undated (Box 24, Folder 12)
  - Higher Education Program Bulletin, undated (Box 24, Folder 13)
  - Higher Education Resource, undated (Box 24, Folder 14)
  - Hill, Lisa, undated (Box 24, Folder 15)
  - Hill, W. Nick, undated (Box 24, Folder 16)
  - Hindle Report, undated (Box 24, Folder 17)
  - Hispanie Resources, undated (Box 24, Folder 18)
  - Historically Black Colleges, undated (Box 24, Folder 19)
  - History of the Hall of Fame, undated (Box 24, Folder 20)
  - Hittner Property, undated (Box 24, Folder 21)
  - Hogeler, Paul, undated (Box 24, Folder 22)
  - Hoffman, Roy, undated (Box 24, Folder 23)
  - Hoffenberg, Raymond, undated (Box 24, Folder 24)
  - Holley, Merle, undated (Box 24, Folder 25)
  - Hook, Sidney, undated (Box 24, Folder 26)
  - Horizon Magazine, undated (Box 24, Folder 27)
  - Hornstein, George, undated (Box 24, Folder 28)
  - Horowitz, Helen, undated (Box 24, Folder 29)
  - Horton, Sheryl, undated (Box 24, Folder 30)
  - Hospital Financing, undated (Box 24, Folder 31)
  - Hospital for Joint Diseases, undated (Box 24, Folder 32)
  - Hotzler, Russell, undated (Box 24, Folder 33)
  - Housing, undated (Box 24, Folder 34)
  - Housing, undated (Box 24, Folder 35)
  - Housing Procedures and Policies, undated (Box 24, Folder 36)
  - Housing University Faculty, undated (Box 24, Folder 37)
  - Huang, Alice, undated (Box 24, Folder 38)
  - Huang, Alice, undated (Box 24, Folder 39)
  - Hughes Proposal, undated (Box 24, Folder 40)
  - Hunter, Jaquelyn, undated (Box 24, Folder 41)
  - Inghilest, Marcello, undated (Box 24, Folder 42)
  - Innovax, 1987 (Box 24, Folder 43)
  - Institute for East-West Security, undated (Box 24, Folder 44)
  - Institute of Public Health, undated (Box 24, Folder 45)
  - Interdisciplinary Science at NYU, undated (Box 24, Folder 46)
  - International Association of Universities, undated (Box 24, Folder 47)
  - International Festival of Puppet Theater, undated (Box 24, Folder 48)
  - International Management Program, undated (Box 24, Folder 49)
  - International Newsletter, undated (Box 24, Folder 50)
  - Invitation, undated (Box 24, Folder 51)
  - Invitation Lists - Irish House, undated (Box 24, Folder 52)
  - Ireland - Fulbright Scholarship, undated (Box 24, Folder 53)
  - Ireland House, undated (Box 24, Folder 54)
  - Ireland House, undated (Box 24, Folder 55)
  - Ireland House, undated (Box 24, Folder 56)
  - Ireland House, undated (Box 24, Folder 57)
  - Ireland House, undated (Box 24, Folder 58)
  - Ireland House, 1991 (Box 24, Folder 59)
  - Ireland House, 1991 (Box 24, Folder 60)
  - Ireland House - Oliva's Trip, undated (Box 25, Folder 1)
    barcode: 3 1142 04058452 9
  - Ireland House - Opening, undated (Box 25, Folder 2)
  - Ireland House - Opening, undated (Box 25, Folder 3)
  - Ireland House - Proposal, undated (Box 25, Folder 4)
  - Irish American Cultural Institute, undated (Box 25, Folder 5)
  - Irish Studies, undated (Box 25, Folder 6)
  - Iselin, J., undated (Box 25, Folder 7)
  - Isozaki, Arata, undated (Box 25, Folder 8)
  - Italian Journal, 1989 (Box 25, Folder 9)
  - Italian Trade Commission, undated (Box 25, Folder 10)
  - Jackson, Weldon, undated (Box 25, Folder 11)
  - Jacobs, Andrew, undated (Box 25, Folder 12)
  - Jamzadeh, Mehrnaz, undated (Box 25, Folder 13)
  - Jeffries, Trelle, undated (Box 25, Folder 14)
  - Jewish Cultural Foundation, undated (Box 25, Folder 15)
  - Jewish Holidays, undated (Box 25, Folder 16)
  - Jewish Studies, undated (Box 25, Folder 17)
  - Jewish Studies Search, undated (Box 25, Folder 18)
  - Johns Hopkins Medical Institution, undated (Box 25, Folder 19)
  - Johnson, Alonzo, undated (Box 25, Folder 20)
  - Joint Projects, undated (Box 25, Folder 21)
  - Joans, Robert, undated (Box 25, Folder 22)
  - Judaic Studies Program - Brown University, undated (Box 25, Folder 23)
  - Judson Church, undated (Box 25, Folder 24)
  - Judson Church, 1969-1986 (Box 25, Folder 25)
  - Judson Church - Law School, 1984 (Box 25, Folder 26)
  - Judson Hall, undated (Box 25, Folder 27)
  - Judt, Tony, undated (Box 25, Folder 28)
  - Julia Reichman High School, undated (Box 25, Folder 29)
  - Kahn, Fern, undated (Box 25, Folder 30)
  - Kalbacker, Warren, undated (Box 25, Folder 31)
  - Kallenbach, Neville, undated (Box 25, Folder 32)
  - Kantor, J., undated (Box 25, Folder 33)
  - Kaplan, Flora, undated (Box 25, Folder 34)
  - Karp, Edwin, undated (Box 25, Folder 35)
  - Katz, Leslie, undated (Box 25, Folder 36)
  - Kaufman, Ann, undated (Box 25, Folder 37)
  - Kazemi, Farhad, undated (Box 25, Folder 38)
  - Kazin, Alfred, undated (Box 25, Folder 39)
  - Mrs. Kean, undated (Box 25, Folder 40)
  - Keefe, Robert, undated (Box 25, Folder 41)
  - Kinnell, Galway, undated (Box 25, Folder 42)
  - Kips Bay - 1, undated (Box 25, Folder 43)
  - Kips Bay - 2, undated (Box 25, Folder 44)
  - Kips Bay - 3, undated (Box 25, Folder 45)
  - Kips Bay - 4, undated (Box 25, Folder 46)
  - Kips Bay Budget File, undated (Box 25, Folder 47)
  - Kips Bay Cherry Letter, undated (Box 25, Folder 48)
  - Kips Bay Easements, undated (Box 26, Folder 1)
    barcode: 3 1142 04058453 7
  - Kips Bay Horowitz, undated (Box 26, Folder 2)
  - Kips Bay Morse-Diesel Contract, undated (Box 26, Folder 3)
  - Kips Bay Real Estate, undated (Box 26, Folder 4)
  - Kips Bay Staff Residence, undated (Box 26, Folder 5)
  - Kirshenblatt-Gimblett, B., undated (Box 26, Folder 6)
  - Kiss, Maryland, undated (Box 26, Folder 7)
  - Kittay, Jeff, undated (Box 26, Folder 8)
  - Kivetz, Robert, undated (Box 26, Folder 9)
  - Klinger, Mary, undated (Box 26, Folder 10)
  - Knickman, James, undated (Box 26, Folder 11)
  - Kobren, Dr. Abraham, undated (Box 26, Folder 12)
  - Koch, Ed, undated (Box 26, Folder 13)
  - Koch, Stephen, undated (Box 26, Folder 14)
  - Koerner, Diana, undated (Box 26, Folder 15)
  - Kolb, Barbara, undated (Box 26, Folder 16)
  - Koppenaal, Richard, undated (Box 26, Folder 17)
  - Kovner, Anthony, undated (Box 26, Folder 18)
  - Kriser, David, undated (Box 26, Folder 19)
  - Kriser, David - Visiting Professorship, 1978-1979 (Box 26, Folder 20)
  - Kriser, David - Visiting Professorship, 1981-1982 (Box 26, Folder 21)
  - Kriser, David - Visiting Professorship, 1984 (Box 26, Folder 22)
  - Kriser, David - Visiting Professorship, 1987-1989 (Box 26, Folder 23)
  - Kriser, David - Visiting Professorship, 1991-1992 (Box 26, Folder 24)
  - Kristeller, Paul, undated (Box 26, Folder 25)
  - Kurahari, Korehiro, undated (Box 26, Folder 26)
  - Labatt, Deidre, undated (Box 26, Folder 27)
  - Lafayette Street - 295 Puck Building, undated (Box 26, Folder 28)
  - LaGuardia Place - 552-556, undated (Box 26, Folder 29)
  - LaGuardia Strips, undated (Box 26, Folder 30)
  - LAN Building List, undated (Box 26, Folder 31)
  - Langfitt, Thomas W., undated (Box 26, Folder 32)
  - Langford, George, undated (Box 26, Folder 33)
  - La Rue, Jan, undated (Box 26, Folder 34)
  - LaSalle, Dorothy T., undated (Box 26, Folder 35)
  - Law Center Foundation, undated (Box 26, Folder 36)
  - Lawrence, Jacob, undated (Box 26, Folder 37)
  - Lawrence, Jacob, undated (Box 26, Folder 38)
  - Law School Budgets, undated (Box 26, Folder 39)
  - Law School - Benjamin Thompson Associates, undated (Box 26, Folder 40)
  - Law School Construction, undated (Box 26, Folder 41)
  - Law School Construction Brady, undated (Box 26, Folder 42)
  - Law School Correspondence, undated (Box 26, Folder 43)
  - Law School Expansion, undated (Box 27, Folder 1)
    barcode: 3 1142 4058454 5
  - Law School Faculty Housing, undated (Box 27, Folder 2)
    barcode: 3 1142 04058454 5
  - Law School Land Valuations, undated (Box 27, Folder 3)
  - Law School Miscellaneous, undated (Box 27, Folder 4)
  - Law School Planning Academic Site, 1982 (Box 27, Folder 5)
  - Law School Residence Hall, undated (Box 27, Folder 6)
  - Law School Residence Hall Financial Matters, undated (Box 27, Folder 7)
  - Law School Residence Hall Furnishings, undated (Box 27, Folder 8)
  - Law School Residence Hall - Mercer Street Dorm, undated (Box 27, Folder 9)
  - Law School Residence Hall - Mercer Street Rental Analysis, undated (Box 27, Folder 10)
  - Law School Residence Hall - Planning, Construction, and Zoning, undated (Box 27, Folder 11)
  - Law School Residence Hall - Site Acquisition, undated (Box 27, Folder 12)
  - Law School Residence Hall - Site Acquisition Costs, undated (Box 27, Folder 13)
  - Law School Tenent Relocation, 1982 (Box 27, Folder 14)
  - Law School - Tischman Construction Company, undated (Box 27, Folder 15)
  - Lax, Anneli, undated (Box 27, Folder 16)
  - Leadership, undated (Box 27, Folder 17)
  - Leadership Alliance, 1994 (Box 27, Folder 18)
  - Leepson, Peter, undated (Box 27, Folder 19)
  - Lennon Center for Popular Culture, undated (Box 27, Folder 20)
  - Leontief, Wassily, undated (Box 27, Folder 21)
  - Levine, Naomi, undated (Box 27, Folder 22)
  - Liberty Partnership Program, undated (Box 27, Folder 23)
  - Licensing, undated (Box 27, Folder 24)
  - List, Claire, undated (Box 27, Folder 25)
  - Litigation - Tenant Relocation, undated (Box 27, Folder 26)
  - Little Italy Project, undated (Box 27, Folder 27)
  - Little Red School House, undated (Box 27, Folder 28)
  - LJO Weeklies, 1989 (Box 27, Folder 29)
  - LJO Weeklies, 1989-1990 (Box 27, Folder 30)
  - Loeb Student Center, 1986 (Box 28, Folder 1)
    barcode: 3 1142 04058455 2
  - London Avis Telecommunications, undated (Box 28, Folder 2)
  - Lopez - Isa, Jose, undated (Box 28, Folder 3)
  - Lorca - Isabel Garcia, undated (Box 28, Folder 4)
  - Loring Place - 1971, undated (Box 28, Folder 5)
  - Loring Place - 2202, undated (Box 28, Folder 6)
  - Lowe, Anthony, undated (Box 28, Folder 7)
  - Luce - Scholars Program, undated (Box 28, Folder 8)
  - Luther, Sheldon, undated (Box 28, Folder 9)
  - MacDougal Street, undated (Box 28, Folder 10)
  - MacDougal Street, undated (Box 28, Folder 11)
  - MacDougal Street - 134, undated (Box 28, Folder 12)
  - MacDougal Street - 135, undated (Box 28, Folder 13)
  - Magazine of Higher Learning, 1987 (Box 28, Folder 14)
  - Major, Donald, undated (Box 28, Folder 15)
  - Mahomed, Ismail, undated (Box 28, Folder 16)
  - Maimonides Property, undated (Box 28, Folder 17)
  - Main Block - Juster, undated (Box 28, Folder 18)
  - Malamud, Bernard, undated (Box 28, Folder 19)
  - Mangum, Anne, undated (Box 28, Folder 20)
  - Mann, Nicholas, undated (Box 28, Folder 21)
  - Mannes Institute, undated (Box 28, Folder 22)
  - Manning, George, undated (Box 28, Folder 23)
  - Marcel, David, undated (Box 28, Folder 24)
  - Martin, Nancy Archer, undated (Box 28, Folder 25)
  - Masco, Lorie, undated (Box 28, Folder 26)
  - Mastersons, Patrick, undated (Box 28, Folder 27)
  - Mastrogiovanni, R. Gabe, undated (Box 28, Folder 28)
  - Matthias, Charles, undated (Box 28, Folder 29)
  - Matte, Sata, undated (Box 28, Folder 30)
  - Maxwell, Robert Scholars Proposal, undated (Box 28, Folder 31)
  - Mayor's Commission for Science and Technology, 1988-1989 (Box 28, Folder 32)
  - Malik, Mazhar Ali Khan, undated (Box 28, Folder 33)
  - McGinnes, Junior R.S., undated (Box 28, Folder 34)
  - McCintosh, David S., undated (Box 28, Folder 35)
  - McClaren, Andrew, undated (Box 28, Folder 36)
  - Media Group, undated (Box 28, Folder 37)
  - Medical Center Institute of Physical Medicine and Rehabilitation, undated (Box 28, Folder 38)
  - Medical Center Mobil Gas Station, undated (Box 28, Folder 39)
  - Medical Center Pomerance Plan, undated (Box 28, Folder 40)
  - Medical Center Schal Associates, undated (Box 28, Folder 41)
  - Medical Center Scientific Laborotary, undated (Box 28, Folder 42)
  - Medical Center Site Plans, undated (Box 28, Folder 43)
  - Medical Center Thirty Fourth Street Project, undated (Box 28, Folder 44)
  - Medical and Dental Humanities Project, undated (Box 28, Folder 45)
  - Mellon Foundation Proposal, undated (Box 28, Folder 46)
  - Menus, undated (Box 28, Folder 47)
  - Metz, Ilena, undated (Box 28, Folder 48)
  - Middlesex County College, undated (Box 28, Folder 49)
  - Middle States, 1988 (Box 28, Folder 50)
  - Middle States Academic Affairs, undated (Box 28, Folder 51)
  - Miller, Dee, undated (Box 28, Folder 52)
  - Minority Graduate Education Project, undated (Box 28, Folder 53)
  - Minority Recruitment, undated (Box 29, Folder 1)
    barcode: 3 1142 04058456 0
  - Miropolskaya, Mara, 1989 (Box 29, Folder 2)
  - Mitchell, Dawn A., undated (Box 29, Folder 3)
  - Mitt - Kudos, undated (Box 29, Folder 4)
  - Modern European Studies Proposal - Mellon Foundation, undated (Box 29, Folder 5)
  - Modern Language Association, undated (Box 29, Folder 6)
  - Montorio, John, undated (Box 29, Folder 7)
  - Moody, Betty, undated (Box 29, Folder 8)
  - Moore, Michael, undated (Box 29, Folder 9)
  - Moorty, Ammini, undated (Box 29, Folder 10)
  - Morgan Library, undated (Box 29, Folder 11)
  - Morrison, Toni, undated (Box 29, Folder 12)
  - Morrow, Carrol, undated (Box 29, Folder 13)
  - Movshon, J. Anthony, undated (Box 29, Folder 14)
  - Mowder, Williams, undated (Box 29, Folder 15)
  - Mullet, Donald, undated (Box 29, Folder 16)
  - Multiculturalism, undated (Box 29, Folder 17)
  - Museum of the City of New York, undated (Box 29, Folder 18)
  - Museum Studies Projects and Proposals, undated (Box 29, Folder 19)
  - Munoz, Arlene, undated (Box 29, Folder 20)
  - Music Performance Committee, 1992 (Box 29, Folder 21)
  - Music Performance Committee, 1993 (Box 29, Folder 22)
  - Music Performance Report, undated (Box 29, Folder 23)
  - Music - Search - Results, undated (Box 29, Folder 24)
  - Mutz, John M., undated (Box 29, Folder 25)
  - Named Classroom - Fourth St. 25 West, undated (Box 29, Folder 26)
  - Named Classroom - Shimkin Hall, undated (Box 29, Folder 27)
  - Named Professorships, 1990 (Box 29, Folder 28)
  - Namy, Joseph, undated (Box 29, Folder 29)
  - National Arts Club, undated (Box 29, Folder 30)
  - National Arts Education Research Center, undated (Box 29, Folder 31)
  - National Arts Education Research Center SEHNAP, undated (Box 29, Folder 32)
  - National Association of Independent Colleges and Universities, undated (Box 29, Folder 33)
  - National Board for Professional Teaching Standards, undated (Box 29, Folder 34)
  - National Book Critics Circle, undated (Box 29, Folder 35)
  - National Center for History in Schools, undated (Box 29, Folder 36)
  - National Crime Prevention Council, undated (Box 29, Folder 37)
  - NEA, undated (Box 29, Folder 38)
  - NEH, 1990 (Box 29, Folder 39)
  - NEH, 1991 (Box 29, Folder 40)
  - NEH - American Experience, undated (Box 29, Folder 41)
  - NES - National Executive Service Corp, undated (Box 29, Folder 42)
  - NFE - National Faculty Exchange, undated (Box 29, Folder 43)
  - National Science Foundation, undated (Box 29, Folder 44)
  - National Science Foundation Proposal, undated (Box 29, Folder 45)
  - National Science Foundation Proposal/Alliances for Minority Participation, undated (Box 29, Folder 46)
  - National Science Foundation Proposal/Alliances for Minority Participation, 1990 (Box 29, Folder 47)
  - Nazzal, Nafez, undated (Box 29, Folder 48)
  - Neipris, Cynthia, undated (Box 29, Folder 49)
  - Nelkin, Dorothy, undated (Box 29, Folder 50)
  - Nelson, Clifford, undated (Box 29, Folder 51)
  - Nelson, Rosemary, undated (Box 29, Folder 52)
  - New York Academy of Sciencies, 1988-1989 (Box 29, Folder 53)
  - New York ACT advisory council, undated (Box 29, Folder 54)
  - New York Children's Health Project, undated (Box 29, Folder 55)
  - New York City Board of Ed, undated (Box 29, Folder 56)
  - New York City Parks and Recreation, undated (Box 29, Folder 57)
  - New York City Technical College, undated (Box 29, Folder 58)
  - New York Public Library, undated (Box 29, Folder 59)
  - New York Shakespeare Festival, undated (Box 29, Folder 60)
  - New York State Council on Languages, undated (Box 29, Folder 61)
  - New York Times, 1988 (Box 30, Folder 1)
    barcode: 3 1142 04058457 8
  - New York University Construction, 1955-1980 (Box 30, Folder 2)
  - New York University Press Releases, undated (Box 30, Folder 3)
  - Nichols Property, undated (Box 30, Folder 4)
  - Ninth Street - 60 East 30-40, 1980-1982 (Box 30, Folder 5)
  - Ninth Avenue - 58 and 60th, 1976-1977 (Box 30, Folder 6)
  - Njogu, Karambu, undated (Box 30, Folder 7)
  - Norich, Samuel, undated (Box 30, Folder 8)
  - North Side, undated (Box 30, Folder 9)
  - NSF Proposal, 1991 (Box 30, Folder 10)
  - NYU: Affairs, undated (Box 30, Folder 11)
  - NYU: Bulletins, undated (Box 30, Folder 12)
  - NYU: Camp, undated (Box 30, Folder 13)
  - NYU: EMS, undated (Box 30, Folder 14)
  - NYU: Emergency Translator Service, undated (Box 30, Folder 15)
  - NYU: Endowed Chairs, 1989 (Box 30, Folder 16)
  - NYU: Family Cookbook, undated (Box 30, Folder 17)
  - NYU: Founders Day, 1988-1991 (Box 30, Folder 18)
  - NYU: Founders Day, 1992 (Box 30, Folder 19)
  - NYU: Funding Opportunities Brochure, undated (Box 30, Folder 20)
  - NYU: Fundraising Speeches, undated (Box 30, Folder 21)
  - NYU: Funds to Develop University, undated (Box 30, Folder 22)
  - NYU: Give a Violet, undated (Box 30, Folder 23)
  - NYU: Gospel Choir, undated (Box 30, Folder 24)
  - NYU: Government Relations, 1989-1990 (Box 30, Folder 25)
  - NYU: Grading System, 1988 (Box 30, Folder 26)
  - NYU: Graduate and Professional Opportunity Fellowship, undated (Box 30, Folder 27)
  - NYU: Graduate Commission Recommendation, undated (Box 30, Folder 28)
  - NYU: Graduate Feminist Forum, undated (Box 30, Folder 29)
  - NYU: Great Teachers, undated (Box 30, Folder 30)
  - NYU: History, undated (Box 30, Folder 31)
  - NYU: I Have a Dream Project, undated (Box 30, Folder 32)
  - NYU: IBM, undated (Box 30, Folder 33)
  - NYU: Innauguration: LJO, undated (Box 30, Folder 34)
  - NYU: Innauguration: Thank you Letters, undated (Box 30, Folder 35)
  - NYU: Industry Specific Programs, undated (Box 30, Folder 36)
  - NYU: Library, undated (Box 30, Folder 37)
  - NYU: Listening Post Group, undated (Box 30, Folder 38)
  - NYU: Mail Service, undated (Box 30, Folder 39)
  - NYU: Major Special Events, undated (Box 30, Folder 40)
  - NYU: Manhattan South Magazine, undated (Box 30, Folder 41)
  - NYU: MLK, Jr. Scholars, undated (Box 30, Folder 42)
  - NYU: Named Classroom Project, undated (Box 30, Folder 43)
  - NYU: Needs Attention, undated (Box 30, Folder 44)
  - NYU: Occupational Therapy, undated (Box 30, Folder 45)
  - NYU: Office of Health Affairs, undated (Box 30, Folder 46)
  - NYU: Oxford, undated (Box 30, Folder 47)
  - NYU: Senate Academic Affairs Committee, undated (Box 30, Folder 48)
  - NYU: Senate Academic Affairs Meeting, 1990 (Box 30, Folder 49)
  - NYU: Senate and Facult Relations Committee, undated (Box 30, Folder 50)
  - NYU: Senate and University, undated (Box 30, Folder 51)
  - NYU: Senate, 1989 (Box 30, Folder 52)
  - NYU: Senate Committee, 1990 (Box 30, Folder 53)
  - NYU: Senate, 1992 (Box 30, Folder 54)
  - NYU: Senate, 1993 (Box 30, Folder 55)
  - NYU: Senate, 1993-1994 (Box 30, Folder 56)
  - NYU: Senate, 1996 (Box 30, Folder 57)
  - NYU: Statement of Institutional Mission, undated (Box 30, Folder 58)
  - NYU: Today, undated (Box 30, Folder 59)
  - NYU: Undergraduate Guide to Opportunities, undated (Box 30, Folder 60)
  - NYU: Universities Associates List, undated (Box 30, Folder 61)
  - NYU: Universities Community Letter, undated (Box 30, Folder 62)
  - NYU: University Facilities, undated (Box 30, Folder 63)
  - NYU: University Senate, undated (Box 30, Folder 64)
  - NYU: Visit of Daithio'caelligh, undated (Box 30, Folder 65)
  - NYU: Vladeck Fellows, undated (Box 30, Folder 66)
  - O'Connor, Sally, undated (Box 31, Folder 1)
    barcode: 3 1142 04058458 6
  - O'Heocha, Colm, undated (Box 31, Folder 2)
  - Oaks, John, undated (Box 31, Folder 3)
  - Odden, Allan (USC), undated (Box 31, Folder 4)
  - Odom, Evelyn, undated (Box 31, Folder 5)
  - Office of Sponsored Programs, undated (Box 31, Folder 6)
  - Olds, Sharon, undated (Box 31, Folder 7)
  - Oliva, Lawrence Jay, undated (Box 31, Folder 8)
  - Onassis, undated (Box 31, Folder 9)
  - Onassis Center-Proposal, undated (Box 31, Folder 10)
  - Onassis Foundation/L Berlowitz, undated (Box 31, Folder 11)
  - Onassis, General Correspondence, undated (Box 31, Folder 12)
  - Onassis Foundation Miscellaneous, undated (Box 31, Folder 13)
  - Onassis Foundation Reports I, undated (Box 31, Folder 14)
  - Onassis Foundation Reports II, undated (Box 31, Folder 15)
  - Onassis Foundation Reports III, undated (Box 31, Folder 16)
  - Oppenheim, David/Retirement Songbook, undated (Box 31, Folder 17)
  - Oxford University Faculty Exchange Program with NYU, undated (Box 31, Folder 18)
  - Oxford University Press, undated (Box 31, Folder 19)
  - Palladio Exhibition, undated (Box 31, Folder 20)
  - Parallel Lines Productions, undated (Box 31, Folder 21)
  - Papp, Joe/Biographical Articles, undated (Box 31, Folder 22)
  - Pasolini, undated (Box 31, Folder 23)
  - Patterson, Evelynn, undated (Box 31, Folder 24)
  - Payne, Carleen, undated (Box 31, Folder 25)
  - Penn, Harry, undated (Box 31, Folder 26)
  - Perucic, Jasna, undated (Box 31, Folder 27)
  - Peruggi, Regina, undated (Box 31, Folder 28)
  - Peters, F.E., undated (Box 31, Folder 29)
  - Petriello, Richard, undated (Box 31, Folder 30)
  - PEW Charitable Trust, undated (Box 31, Folder 31)
  - PEW Science Program, undated (Box 31, Folder 32)
  - Pfenninger, Kally, undated (Box 31, Folder 33)
  - Phillips, Mona, undated (Box 31, Folder 34)
  - Phipps Plaza East, 1973 (Box 31, Folder 35)
  - Pickett, Sharon, undated (Box 31, Folder 36)
  - Picnic, undated (Box 31, Folder 37)
  - Piersa, Bob, undated (Box 31, Folder 38)
  - Planning and Construction Bid Information, 1996-2003 (Box 31, Folder 39)
  - Planning Comission Summary, 1988 (Box 31, Folder 40)
  - Podehorzer, Norman, undated (Box 31, Folder 41)
  - Poincelot, Raymond P, undated (Box 31, Folder 42)
  - Polowczyk, Carl J, undated (Box 31, Folder 43)
  - Port Imperial Ferry, undated (Box 31, Folder 44)
  - President's Comission on White House Fellowships, undated (Box 31, Folder 45)
  - President's Committee on the Arts and the Humanities I, undated (Box 31, Folder 46)
  - President's Committee on the Arts and the Humanities II, undated (Box 31, Folder 47)
  - President's Conference Room (PCR) Reservations, undated (Box 31, Folder 48)
  - Presidential Fellowship/Agreement to Review Letters, 1992 (Box 31, Folder 49)